Can you see it? The tears in these eyes
are blurring into the colours of my life.
What have I left to give you?
I ask the question, I cease to function...
Blue, red and white mix
I am shouting in this world.
What am I seeking out?
I'm tired of chasing...
How much am I abnormal?
Am I broken?
I'm broken all right.
Even so, I want, I want to breathe.
Can you see me,
like I'm in a dream? Even my final
word is stuck!
It happened a long time ago.
A faint light is flooding the sky
What did I choose and line up?
Colours of tears are overlaid.
That floating body
dissolves and blurs inside my consciousness
What did I come to see and compare?
I'm sad and I forget...
How much am I abnormal?
Am I distorted?
I'm distorted all right
Even so, I want, I want to breathe
I'm having a dream
To you who are in my thoughts, even my final
word to you is stuck!
Translation: ElectricRaichu
Can I neither give, lose, or forget?
This error that's going beserk,
I kill it and laugh, and again, an error.
Did I break it?
Do you know it's broken?
Even so, my tears hurt, they hurt.
Have they reached you?
Even though my final words
are lined up in my singing voice,
the overlapping colours blur...
Am I broken?
I'm broken all right
Even so, I want, I want to breathe.
You've seen me,
like I was in a dream. Even my final
word is stuck!