A blade's edge with centimeters of suspicion
Stabbing a vein at the end of it all
Sticky love spurts out
Even my Les Paul became a deadly weapon
It's no-fiction
I like math and science
But I was never one for Japanese
I'd worry about which answer was right
Jokes on me, both were wrong
Today's homework is my basic self
With just enough  with no complaints Living in the nowadays
But why do we sometimes-- no, always
Say we're sad, say we're lonely
Can you read the kanji on the board?
Can you read the shape of this kid's heart?
Who stained that heart black?
Who was it? Who was it!?
Can you do this problem on an abacus?
Can you undo this collar around this kid's neck?
Can we keep going like this?
What're you gonna do?
I don't care anymore!
All this time we were
Under a crude hyponosis
Holding an incredible arrogrance
Hidden inside
Can't do yesterday's homework as always
With just enough  with no complaints Living in the nowadays
But why does this lump in our hearts
Say we want to disappear?
Say we want to die?
Can you read the kanji on the board?
Can you read the shape of this kid's heart?
Who stained that heart black?
Hey! Who was it? Who was it!?
Can you do this problem on an abacus?
Can you undo this collar on this kid's neck?
Can we keep going like this?
What're you gonna do?
Do you remember the formula for area ratio?
Do you remember the dreams of your childhood?
Who threw those dreams in a ditch?
Who was it!?
You know who it was!
When are you gonna grow up?
What is a grown-up anyway?
Who has the answers?
What're you gonna do?
Can you read the kanji on the board?
Can you read the shape of this kid's heart?
Who stained that heart black?
Who was it? Who was it!?
Can you do this problem on an abacus?
Can you undo this collar on this kid's neck?
Can we keep going like this?
What're you gonna do?
I don't care anymore!