What seems to be endless
Pointless colorless
It's a mess, you know
This hopeless life of mine
No friends to be with
I'm really so jealous of all the beautiful colors of yours
Heavy shadows, scary nightfall erase all the lines I've got
I want to scream but can't open my mouth
A broken piece of chalk is enough to connect the dots
Because I'm still alive
There must be a meaning, right?
People in this world are colorful
The ugly and the beautiful
Make up colors in this world
Hey
Just pick up your pencil, crayons
And be colorful
I'm sure this world is wonderful
Showered in happiness
My blossoming friendship
It's a bless, I know
Your kindness led my way
'Cause of my wariness
I was so blinded from all the unusual colors of mine
To think that I was so scared over nothing at all
I guess I was too young to know myself
In the future even if my lines are all tangled up
I'll still be alive
And that's what matters, right?
People in this world are incredible
So strong and so admirable
Each one is a miracle
Hey
Just pick up your pencil, crayons
And stay colorful
You see? This world is wonderful
Even though I may not be able to erase all my mistakes
I can paint on another page
Because everyone around you have always lived that way
There's so much to your life
Everything will be all right
People, people in this world are colorful
The ugly and the beautiful
Make up colors in this world
Hey
Just pick up your pencil, crayons
And be colorful
Because this world is wonderful