The plug on my headphones remains barren.
Anyway, for now, I want to isolate myself from this world.
From time to time, there's the sound of the wind. I close my eyes. Darkness.
No one comes interfere, in my own little area.
"There's no way I'm actually bluffing, right?,"
I tell myself, I tell myself.
How far will I walk?
"I'm lonely"? I wouldn't say that even if you pried off my lips.
Because, because,
if they think of me as "that poor thing," It'd be shameful
"I bet they hate you, huh?"
Not so, I just like being alone.
Because, because,
if I don't pretend I do,
it means I'm already broken.
"Don't touch me." the balsam, fallen silent.
And yet it can't leave seeds unless it breaks it's shell
Everyone looks merry, while I'm the only one outside the circle
If i'd been in from the start, i wonder if that'd have made a difference
Rather than wandering around, not a part of anything
standing boldly independent
looks a lot cooler, doesn't it?
"Let me into your group?" I wouldn't say that even if you pried off my lips
Because, because,
my pride won't allow that.
I don't think, "I envy them." I don't want to.
Then, I may as well-
I don't want any friends,
just give me a heart that won't break.
You can't even go to the bathroom by yourself,
I cursed them,
as I followed them out of the corner of my eye.
"I'm lonely?" I wouldn't say that even if you pried my lips off
Because, because,
if they think of me as "that poor thing," I'll be the loser
"I bet they hate you, huh?"
No, I just like being alone.
Because, because,
If I don't pretend that I do,
it means I'm already broken
Translation by zcatcracker